<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>inSileco</title><link>https://www.insileco.io/</link><description>Recent content on inSileco</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.insileco.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About us</title><link>https://www.insileco.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.insileco.io/about/</guid><description>We are three
David Beauchesne (co-founder) I am one of the founders of inSileco and a postdoctoral researcher at Université Laval. I am an ecologist working on ecosystem-based management in general and cumulative effects assessments in particular, with a focus on open science, reproducibility and computational tools. Kevin Cazelles (co-founder) Co-fonder of inSileco, associate researcher at the University of Guelph, open and reproducible research advocate. For almost ten years now, I have been tackling research challenges in various areas of ecology.</description></item><item><title>Education</title><link>https://www.insileco.io/education/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.insileco.io/education/</guid><description>This is what we have done so far.
Interactive Raster Visualization with R Bedford Institute of Oceanography, Fisheries and Oceans Canada [https://github.com/inSilecoInc/workshop_raster https://github.com/inSilecoInc/interactiveRaster] Reproducible Workflows. Increase Everyday Efficiency Bedford Institute of Oceanography, Fisheries and Oceans Canada https://insilecoinc.github.io/workshop_reproducibility/ Working and visualizing spatial data with R Canadian Wildlife Service, Environment and Climate Change Canada https://insilecoinc.github.io/wksh_raster_CWS/ Work more collaboratively in R with git and GitHub Bedford Institute of Oceanography, Fisheries and Oceans Canada https://github.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://www.insileco.io/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.insileco.io/projects/</guid><description>The projects that we have been involved with as scientists, as members of inSileco, or both.</description></item></channel></rss>